noahslist.com 2012-02-19

# Classifieds Noahslist.com - Noahslist.com

noahslist.com Classifieds is committed to safeguarding your online privacy. The following policy outlines how your personal information will be treated as you use our website.

noahslist.com Classifieds may update this privacy policy from time to time, in order to take into account new laws and technology or to reflect changes in our operations. All personal information held by Sell Local will be governed by noahslist.com Classifieds most recent policy which will be displayed on this site.

**1\. What personal information do we collect?**

noahslist.com Classifieds primarily collects personal information from its users during the registration process. We collect and store users' names, email addresses, contact numbers and usernames and also other information including user's IP addresses and standard web log information. If a user contacts noahslist.com Classifieds via email, a record of that correspondence may also be stored.

noahslist.com Classifieds may place a cookie in the browser files of a user's computer. We use cookies to save information you give us so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. This allows us to personalize the site to your taste and provide the best web experience possible to our users. We do not use cookies to track your movements on different web sites and do not exchange cookies with other entities.

**2\. How do we use your personal information?**

noahslist.com Classifieds uses the information collected to:

  * Provide the products or services requested;
  * Communicate with our users;
  * Manage and enhance our services;
  * Resolve disputes and troubleshooting;
  * Measure interest in our services.

**3\. Disclosure**

noahslist.com Classifieds may provide your information to law enforcement to aid in their investigations of illegal or fraudulent postings. If noahslist.com Classifieds sells part or all of its business, personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the purchaser.

**4\. How do we treat sensitive information?**

"Sensitive Information" means information relating to a person's racial or ethnic origin, membership of political bodies, religion, membership of a trade union or professional or trade association, sexual preferences, criminal record and health.

noahslist.com Classifieds may use and disclose sensitive information only for the purpose for which it was provided or a directly related secondary purpose or as allowed by law unless you have agreed otherwise.

**5\. Management and security of personal information**

noahslist.com Classifieds protects the personal information it holds from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure by various means including password access and secure servers. Only the privacyistrators of noahslist.com Classifieds and the user have access to that user's personal information. We recommend that users do not disclose their password to anyone.

**6\. Updating personal information**

noahslist.com Classifieds endeavours to ensure that the personal information it holds is accurate, complete and up-to-date. Users can update their information after logging in. Alternatively, users can email [privacy@noahslist.com](mailto:privacy@noahslist.com) to advise of their information updates. Where personal information is no longer required by noahslist.com Classifieds, it will be destroyed or de-identified.

**7\. How to access personal information noahslist.com Classifieds holds about you**

You have the right to seek access to the personal information held about you and to advise noahslist.com Classifieds of any inaccuracy. There are some exceptions to this right set out in the Privacy Act.

If you make an access request, noahslist.com Classifieds will ask you to verify your identity and specify what information you require. noahslist.com Classifieds may charge a fee to cover the costs of meeting your request. To make an access request, please email [privacy@noahslist.com](mailto:privacy@noahslist.com).

**8\. Other information about your online privacy**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online (for example in ads that you post or through email) that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

**9\. How to contact noahslist.com Classifieds**

If you have any enquiries or wish to provide feedback about this policy, please email [privacy@noahslist.com](mailto:privacy@noahslist.com).

Information Best Practices to help Avoid Scams

Noahslist.com sites are locally operated and so are the ads posted in them. The majority of people posting ads on noahslist.com have good intentions to sell, or trade, or purchase. However... this being said, the ad quality and an ad posters verification does not mean it is a potential scam. It is highly recommended to use caution and to deal locally with people regarding your ads postings. It is best if you can meet with in person and preferably in a very public place MEANING WHERE OTHER PEOPLE ARE. USE CAUTION and take a friend with you if at all possible. Potential SCAMMERS, PEOPLE WHO WRITE FAKE CHECKS or MONEY ORDERS or CASHIERS CHECKS can be AVOIDED and NEVER give out personal information such as anything about your children, your social security number, banking information etc.. Use common Sense. By using noahslist.com, you agree that any communication and transaction for your services or Items, or meeting whether by phone or in person or 3rd party or email etc...are solely your responsibility regardless of the results. . 

The Deals just keep getting better! Post Ads Free Now, It`s Easy.   
Noah`s List has a huge audience, your ad will be seen by thousands across North America. So don`t wait, post your ad today!
